<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/photos/photo-00001/</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/images/large/photo-00001.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Photograph by John Braybrooke</image:title>
      <image:caption>An empty powder-blue metal folding chair sits alone on a plaza paved with irregular flagstones and red brick. Behind it, a person in a blue dress walks a small cream-coloured dog on a leash. To the right, a plywood board mounted outdoors displays a historical town map and black-and-white archival photographs. Bright midday sun throws hard shadows across the stone.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/photos/photo-00002/</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/images/large/photo-00002.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Photograph by John Braybrooke</image:title>
      <image:caption>A view through the glass front of a clinic. White and yellow vinyl lettering on the window reads &#39;ACUPUNCTURE&#39;, &#39;SHOCKWAVE&#39; and &#39;ICBC PROVIDER&#39;. Behind and reflected in the glass, a man with closely cropped hair is seen from behind in a dark patterned sweatshirt printed with a &#39;Blue Moose — Hope, British Columbia, Canada&#39; logo. A white moulded chair stands in the foreground while reflections of the street layer over the interior.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/photos/photo-00003/</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/images/large/photo-00003.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Photograph by John Braybrooke</image:title>
      <image:caption>A pale blue ceramic dog bowl, decorated with a black bone and a chevron band and filled with water, rests on a sunlit concrete sidewalk. Beside it stands a black A-frame sandwich board for The Parkside Brewery, illustrated with a yellow iced drink, a lemon slice and a red straw, above the words &#39;PURCHASE … FOR … BEER&#39;. Strong angular shadows cross the pavement.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/photos/photo-00004/</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/images/large/photo-00004.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Photograph by John Braybrooke</image:title>
      <image:caption>Photographed from the sidewalk through a shop window. A black-and-white &#39;OPEN&#39; sign hangs from a beaded chain on a suction cup against the dark glass. Behind it, inside the shop, stands a mannequin of a man in a red mesh tank top, dramatically lit so he seems to gaze out through the glass toward the street.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/photos/photo-00005/</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/images/large/photo-00005.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Photograph by John Braybrooke</image:title>
      <image:caption>Seen from outside through a window, a rounded white soft-toy figure in a pink polka-dot dress stands on an interior sill among other small objects. Green oak-leaf foliage fills the lower foreground, and the building&#39;s orange and yellow walls frame the glass.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/photos/photo-00006/</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/images/large/photo-00006.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Photograph by John Braybrooke</image:title>
      <image:caption>Photographed from below, the corner of a billboard cuts diagonally across a blue sky streaked with thin cloud. A black floodlight reaches out on an arm to light the board, which shows a woman with wind-blown dark hair and white sunglasses, smiling, her image skewed by the steep upward angle.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/photos/photo-00007/</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/images/large/photo-00007.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Photograph by John Braybrooke</image:title>
      <image:caption>A weathered advertising poster behind glass, washed by sunlight and crossed by reflections. It pictures a blonde woman in a white top, eyes closed and smiling, with hands resting on her shoulders. The print has abraded and peeled, and a crumpled scrap of paper sits over the centre of her face. A blue perforated panel runs down the right edge.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/photos/photo-00008/</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://johnbraybrooke.com/images/large/photo-00008.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Photograph by John Braybrooke</image:title>
      <image:caption>Two life-size cardboard cutouts of women&#39;s faces rise just above a dense green hedge, positioned in front of a building&#39;s large windows so they seem to peer over the foliage. The glass behind them reflects trees and a neighbouring building.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
